# **EGOR EGOROV**

WEB DEVELOPMENT



### **PROFILE**

I'm a professional full-stack web developer with excellent analytical skills who is passionate about using modern technologies. My experience ranges from building different kinds of web systems such as eCommerce, CRM and ERP to tailored web development with the implementation of Agile Programming Besns. I'm a professional full-stack web developer with ex

## **EDUCATION**

#### developer

Uni #1 2019 - 2021

## developer

Uni #2 2019 - 2021

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2022 - 2022

developer

Company #1

- Front-end development support of specialized web system£ ® Technical support for developed softwal'm a professional full-stack web developer with excellent analytical skills who is passionate about using m

2022 - 2022

developer

Company #3

® Software development for corporate information systeÄ® Development of technical speci<sup>-</sup>cation£® Development and modi<sup>-</sup>cation of component£® Development and improvement of corporate system functionsk web

## 2022 - 2022

## developer

Company #2

® Software development for corporate information systeÄ®
Development of technical speci<sup>-</sup>cation£® Development and modi<sup>-</sup>cation of component£® Development and improvement of corporate system functionsk web

#### 2022 - 2022

#### wf

Company #1

® Software development for corporate information systeÄ®
Development of technical speci<sup>-</sup>cation£® Development and modi<sup>-</sup>cation of component£® Development and improvement of corporate system functionsk web

#### 2022 - 2022

## wf

Company #3

® Software development for corporate information systeÄ ® Development of technical speci<sup>-</sup>cation£ ® Development and modi<sup>-</sup>cation of component£ ® Development and improvement of corporate system functionsk web

## **SOFT SKILLS**

Tech #6,

## **SKILLS**

Front-end Tech #2, Tech #new,

Back-end Tech #1,

Databases Tech #3,

Other Tech #5,

# **EGOR EGOROV**

**PORTFOLIO** 

# Proj #1

**CRM** 

Austria, 2022

Tech #1, Tech #4, Tech #5,

fine dev;

## Proj#2

Web service

Australia, 2022

Tech #1, Tech #2,

also fine dev;

Thank you for your attention hope to hear you back and have a nice day